landmarkshops.com 2016-11-19

# LandmarkShops

Landmark Online Limited, a company incorporated in British Virgin Islands, having its registered office at 325, Waterfront Drive, Wickham's Cay, Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands (referred to herein as "LandmarkShops", "we", "our" or "us") is committed to protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for www.landmarkshops.com and its related sub-domains, sites, services and tools, or any successor site ("Website"). This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes the ways in which we collect, store, use and protect the information collected due to your use of Website. By providing us with your information you expressly consent to us processing your personal information in accordance with the terms of the Privacy Policy. 

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.**

  1. **Change in the Privacy Policy:** Changes in law or changes in LandmarkShops’ business may require changes to be made to the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time so LandmarkShops encourages you to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any such changes. It is your responsibility to carefully read, agree with the Privacy Policy on each occasion you use the Website and your continued use of the Website shall signify your acceptance to be bound by the latest Privacy Policy.

  2. The Information we collect about you may be broadly described in following categories: 

    1. **Personal Information:** Your name, address, phone number, email address, user name, password, billing and credit card information, order history, feedback, IP address and location, digital device name, type and configuration, details relating to your download of Publications via the Service (including details relating to the time of the download, any interruptions, and the success or failure of the downloads), the URL from which you accessed the Website, demographic information, and other such 'Personal Information'.
    2. **General Information:** We also receive more general information from you as a result of your visits to, and use of, the Website. This general information does not identify you personally, and can include information such as your IP address, the length of time you spend on the Website, your browsing history, and other such 'General Information'.

  3. **Treatment of Personal Information:**  

    1. LandmarkShops collects your Personal Information to enable us, amongst other things, to provide the Website and our Services to you. We take all steps reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Personal Information. If LandmarkShops is sold to a third party, or LandmarkShops otherwise becomes subject to a merger, consolidation or acquisition, it would become necessary for us to transfer your Personal Information to a third party, and in such case LandmarkShops would require that the third party handles your Personal Information with no less care than taken by us.
    2. The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates related to your order. It may also be used to respond to your enquiries and requests. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you'll receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. You can unsubscribe from our email list at any time by following the instructions included at the bottom of each email, or by contacting us via our Website.
    3. Other than as may be required in order to operate the Website, or as otherwise described in the Website Terms and Conditions or these Terms, we disclose your Personal Information to third parties only as reasonably required to protect the rights and safety of ourselves and Website users or as required by law enforcement authorities. LandmarkShops' operational purposes include, without limitation:
      1. LandmarkShops' use of other companies and/or individuals to perform functions on its behalf (e.g. processing credit card payments, providing customer service, data hosting services), and in such circumstances these companies or individuals will be provided access to only such Personal Information required to fulfill their functions (and only on the agreement that they not use your Personal Information for any other purposes); and
      2. Purposes intended to deliver publications to you, verify your account information, verify access to publications, determine whether you meet the minimum system requirements for use of the Service, provide you tailored content and instructions, targeted promotions, provide customer support, and seek your input regarding LandmarkShops and the Website.
    4. To keep your Personal Information safe, we ensure that sensitive and private data exchanges between you and LandmarkShops.com happen over a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)-secured communication channel, and are encrypted and protected with digital signatures. SSL-secured communication channels are specially designed to protect personal and sensitive information (payment details), which is sent over the internet.
    5. Apart from aforesaid, we may use third party service providers to help us operate our business, the Site, or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We will only share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes if you've given us your permission to do so.
    6. You may review or update the Personal Information that LandmarkShops holds in respect of your account by contacting LandmarkShops at support@landmarkshops.com

  4. **Treatment of General Information:** LandmarkShops also collects your General Information to allow us, amongst other things, to better understand our users and improve the layout and functionality of the Website. LandmarkShops may use and disclose anonymous information, including aggregate anonymous information derived from your Personal Information, to inform publishers, partners, trusted affiliates, advertisers, and other interested parties as to the usage habits or characteristics of LandmarkShops' customer base, and to serve any other business purposes.

  5. **Cookies:** LandmarkShops may use cookies, or other technologies, to remember Personal Information or General Information when you use the Website. Cookies are small files or records that LandmarkShops may place on your web browser for collecting information about your activities on the Website, preparing reports, assessing trends, and otherwise monitoring the way in which the Website is being used. This is intended to enhance convenience for you, and to assist LandmarkShops to run an efficient operation. By accepting these Terms, you confirm your consent to LandmarkShops' use of cookies, and other such technologies, for these purposes.

  6. Any information that we collect and store that is personally identifiable is protected using appropriate means, and although LandmarkShops does so, it will not be held responsible for any unauthorised access by third parties.

  7. The Website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that LandmarkShops is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites not operated by LandmarkShops, and cannot guarantee the security of any of your Personal Information collected there. LandmarkShops encourages you to read the privacy statements of each and every third party website that collects your Personal Information.

  8. If you have any questions or feedback about the Privacy Policy, contact us at support@landmarkshops.com

**Questions?:**

Contact us at 800–SHOPS (800–74677)

By Post:    
Landmark Shops    
PO Box: 25030    
Dubai, UAE   

Oops! There was a problem. Please correct the highlighted issues

Or via email

__Email entered is registered already

Or via email

__Your Username or Password is incorrect

We're sorry, we've run into a technical issue. Please try again later.
